https://www.downandconnor.org/terms/

Prayer Resources at Home: Loyola Press
Catechetical Resources at Home: ‘Alive in Christ’
Prayer Resources at Home: Loyola Press
Catechetical Resources at Home: ‘Alive in Christ’
Terms and Conditions of Use for the Diocesan Website
Welcome to the Down and Connor Diocesan Trust website.  If you continue to browse and use this website you are agreeing to comply with the following Terms & Conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy are legally binding and shall take effect immediately on your first use of the website.
We may change and republish the Terms & Conditions at any time so please review this section regularly to note any amendments. Continued use of the site after an update has been made indicates the user’s acceptance of those changes.
Copyright
1.1 All rights, including copyright, in the contents and material of the Diocese of Down and Connor web pages are owned and controlled by the ‘Down and Connor Diocesan Trust’. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. You may not copy, reproduce, republish, download, post, broadcast, transmit, make available to the public or otherwise use the Down and Connor Diocesan website content in any way except for your own personal, non-commercial use. Any other use of the Down and Connor Diocesan website content requires prior written permission from the Diocese of Down and Connor, whereupon, if approved, the appropriate licence may be granted.
1.2 The trade marks, logos, names and images displayed on the Down and Connor Diocesan website are the registered or unregistered trade marks of the Down and Connor Diocesan Trust.
1.3 You shall comply with all copyright laws worldwide in the use of the contents of this website and to prevent any unauthorised access or copying of its contents.  Users may download printed copies of the material displayed on the Down and Connor Diocesan website for personal use only (including use at work); provided that you maintain all copyright notices and other proprietary notices and comply with all confidentiality obligations hereunder.
Liability and Disclaimer
2.1 The Down and Connor Diocesan website content, including the information, names, images, pictures, logos and icons regarding or relating to Down and Connor Diocese, is provided without any representations or any kind of warranty made (whether express or implied by law) to the extent permitted by law, including the implied warranties of non-infringement, security and accuracy.
2.2 While reasonable care has been taken in the preparation of the Down and Connor Diocesan website to ensure that the information contained on them is accurate, there may be technical or factual inaccuracies and typographical errors for which we apologise and we expressly exclude liability for any such inaccuracies, omissions or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law. We reserve the right to make changes and corrections at any time, without notice.
2.3. The Down and Connor Diocesan Trust does not warrant that the functions contained in its website content and any associated services will be uninterrupted or error free, or that any defects will be corrected, or that the site or the server that makes it available are free of viruses or other harmful components.
2.4 To the extent permitted by applicable laws, no liability is accepted for any direct, indirect, incidental, special or consequential loss or damages to any user (whether arising in contract, tort including negligence or otherwise) arising out of or in connection with the use of the Down and Connor Diocesan website or these terms and conditions except for personal injury or death of any person caused by negligence or for fraud.
Third Party Links
3.1 Links contained in the Down and Connor Diocesan website may lead to other external websites. The linked sites are provided for your convenience to provide further information and are not under our control. The Down and Connor Diocesan Trust therefore cannot be held responsible for the contents of those websites or any link contained in a linked site. Linking to other websites does not indicate that the Down and Connor Diocesan Trust agrees with any claims, statement or opinions published by those sites.
Supply of Information
4.1 Although the Down and Connor Diocesan Trust may from time to time monitor or review discussions, postings, transmissions, bulletin boards and the like on its website, it is under no obligation to do so and assumes no responsibility or liability arising from the content of any such locations nor for any error, omission, third party infringement, defamation, obscenity, or inaccuracy contained in any information within such locations on its website.
4.2 We may from time-to-time invite users to submit personal information and/or contributions to the Down and Connor Diocesan website. When submitting any contribution to the Down and Connor Diocesan website, users are prohibited from posting or transmitting any unlawful, defamatory, obscene or scandalous material or any material that constitutes or encourages conduct that would be considered a criminal offence or otherwise violates any law. The Down and Connor Diocesan Trust reserves the right to delete, edit or move any content or materials supplied by you in its absolute discretion and to cancel your registration and access rights at any time and for any reason.
Data Collection
5.1 The Down and Connor Diocesan Trust may collect the domain name and email address of visitors to its website and of those who post contributions on the website or communicate with the Down and Connor Diocesan Trust via email, analyse user activity such as what pages users access or visit and information volunteered by the user.
5.2 The information collected by the Down and Connor Diocesan Trust is used for internal purposes only, to improve the content of its websites, customise the content and/or layout of its websites, notify users about updates or changes to its websites, contacting users for marketing purposes and is not shared with other organisations outside of the Down and Connor Diocesan Trust for commercial purposes.
5.3 Please refer to the privacy policy for further details on how the Down and Connor Diocesan Trust uses personal data transmitted by a user on its website.
Revision of Terms and Conditions
6.1 The Down and Connor Diocesan Trust may at any time revise these terms and conditions without notice by posting changes online. It is the responsibility of users to review all information posted on-line. These changes will be effective and binding from when they appear on this site.
Law
7.1 Your use of this website and any download from it and the operation of these terms and conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Northern Ireland and the UK.
Contact
8.1 If you have a query or comment on any of these terms or conditions please email dataprotection@downandconnor.org
24 May 2018
Registered UK Charity No.: 103983
Contact the Diocese
Safeguarding Office
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Notice
© 2014 - 2020 Diocese of Down and Connor – Designed and Developed by GetOnline Pro
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
